# **SVIATOSLAV SAHNO**



#### Contacts



SviatLight



Sviatoslav Sahno



alex0fasten@gmail.com



+38 (073) 432 62 25

# Languages

Ukrainian: Mother tongue

English: B1

Deutsch: A2

# Summary

My name is Sviatoslav, I'm 19 y.o., and I am recent college graduate. During college I have taken active part in creating and supporting website for my educational establishment. I am passionate about developing sites with awesome and friendly user interface. Have experience in working with JS and React library. Besides everything, I'm active, responsible and have nice soft skills and ready to face hardest tasks.

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html 1/3

### Skills

HTML/Semantic layout

CSS

Git JavaScript React Redux Toolkit

## **Work Experience**

### React DEVELOPER, Expletech Company May 2022 - Present

· Mainly was working with implementing new features.

Bug fixing.

**Technologies:** HTML5, CSS3, SASS, React/Redux, Git **Tools:** GitHub, React Developer Tools, Redux DevTools

### HTML/CSS DEVELOPER, Upwork 2021 - 2022

Adaptive, responsive and cross-browser layout.

Mobile-First layout.

• Writing clean and understandable code, based on requirements.

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Flexbox/Grid, Git

Tools: GitHub, Figma

## Study progress



ELEKS bootcamp JavaScript (React) + HTML/CSS Course March 2022 - May 2022



Web Programming Python and JavaScript CS50 October 2021 - February 2022



React samurai trip September 2021 - November 2021



JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures section Basic JavaScript September 2021 - October 2021

### **Additional Activities**

#### **Water Control**

Developed React App Water Control for improving the quality of life. We created this progect as a team. I was on a project as Team Lead. I was improving teamwork, gave my team tasks, was finding and bug fixing, adding new functionality and improvements.

Technologies: ReactJS, HTML, Module CSS, Firebase, PWA

Deploy link: https://eleks-bootcamp-water-control.netlify.app

Source code: https://github.com/eleks-bootcamp/water-control

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html 2/3

#### **Online Store**

Technologies: ReactJS, HTML, Module CSS, Redux Toolkit

Deploy link: https://online-store-light.netlify.app

Source code: https://github.com/SviatLight/online-store-redux

#### Watch List

Technologies: ReactJS, HTML, CSS, Redux Toolkit, RTK query, React router

Source code: https://github.com/SviatLight/watch-list

# **Education History**

2022 - Present: State University of intellectual technologies and communication, Faculty maintenance of communication devices and office equipment.

2022: Eleks bootcamp. Front-End Online Program.

2018 - 2022: College information technology National University Lviv Polytechnic, Faculty maintenance of communication devices and office equipment.

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html 3/3